WILLIAM Z PARKER

7562 Falcon Trace Court, Jacksonville, FL 32222 | (904) 713-3406 | zakmail89@protonmail.com

Professional Summary

Skilled Uber Driver dedicated to providing exceptional customer service to all customers. Versed in keeping vehicle clean and serviced. Adept at providing top-notch care to passengers and belongings. Earned an EMT license in 2013 and worked in a fast paced med surge environment for 2.5 years. I realized this path was not for me and took a job as a delivery driver at papa johns and started driving Uber. I have been with uber now for 3 years, in the last year I became very interested in coding, hacking, A.I., machine learning, engineering. I decided to start learning code and now I'm hooked, currently I am learning Python3, HTML5, and CSS, and I am pursing an entry level position in the IT industry. Check out my repository at https://github.com/zachwp/Hello-World, just copy and paste the link into your browser.

Skills

- Windows 10/ Linux
- Git distributed version control
- HTML5
- Basic CSS
- Basic Python3
- Patient Assessments
- Patient Care
- Human Anatomy Knowledge
- EMT Certification
- Hands-On Medical Experience
- Skilled Problem Solver

- Customer service relations
- Casting/splinting
- Taking and Recording Vital Signs
- Strong work ethic
- Conflict resolution techniques
- Inventory control and management
- Leadership Skills
- Microsoft office/power point
- Acute Physical Therapy Experience
- Spinal immobilization methods
- Team Worker
- Multi Tasking

Work History

Self Employed 03/2016 to Current

Uber – Jacksonville, Fl

Delivery Driver 12/2015 to 04/2016

papa johns pizza – nocatee, florida

• Contacted customers prior to delivery to confirm and coordinate delivery times.

Patient Care Technician 03/2013 to 12/2015

Memorial Hospital – Jacksonville, Florida

- Answered patient calls for care and feeding.
- Maintained accurate records of patient care, condition, progress and concerns.
- Performed direct patient care aimed at increasing comfort, psycho, social and spiritual well-being by providing
 assistance with personal hygiene, physical comfort, nutrition, elimination, prevention of skin breakdown,
 rehabilitation and safety.
- Assisted with patient transfer and ambulation.
- Provided pre- and post-operative care.
- Supported diagnostic procedures, assisted with technical nursing treatments and entered information in patient records and charts.
- Collects patient specimens and data, including vital signs, input/output and other delegated measurements.
- Assisted nurses with wound care for pressure ulcers, bed sores, and surgical site wounds.
- Answered call lights and aided in patient comfort and safety by adjusting beds, lights, bed rails, pillows, patients'
 clothing and bedside tables/equipment.
- Documents objective data and routine aspects of patient care.

Shift Runner 01/2012 to 11/2012

Domino's – Orange Park, Florida

- Reported to each shift on time and ready to work.
- Communicated openly and honestly with the management team during each shift to ensure it ran smoothly.

Education

GED 2008

Florida State College of Jacksonville - Jacksonville Florida

Emergency Medical Technician

2012

Florida Medical Training Institute - Jacksonville Florida

- EMT Certification
- Hands-On Medical Experience
- CPR Certified
- 2+ Years of Experience

Certifications

- EMT Certification
- Nationally Registered EMT
- BLS And CPR
- Basic Cardiac Monitoring